pdfpro.co 2019-04-22

# PDF Pro | Our Privacy Policy

This policy sets out PDF Pro’s privacy practices in connection with all of the services by us (collectively, "Services").

If you have any questions about this policy, are concerned about how personal data is processed by PDF Pro, or if you wish to receive a copy of any personal data which you may have supplied to us, please **contact us via email: support@pdfpro.co**

**Collection and Use of Information**

PDF Pro does not collect any personal data about you on this website or in connection with any other service, apart from information which you volunteer (for example by e-mailing us, by purchasing a product from us, by downloading a product from us, or by registering your product with us, or by using our online feedback form).

When you purchase a service from us, we may collect information including your contact details and credit card details. Please note that credit card information may be retained by us or our billing provider as a record of any transaction we undertake with you. Information which you provide is used by PDF Pro only in line with the purpose for which you provided it and will not be made available to third parties, other than information provided to us during the purchase process which may be provided to our online billing provider and our banking institution to enable the purchase to be processed.

If PDF Pro has your email address, we may contact you by email to subscribe you to our newsletter or offer you PDF Pro or third party products.

If you upload a file to our service, the data is hosted on a third-party hosting system that is not viewable by PDF Pro. Thus we do not open or view files uploaded to our site. All files stored on our servers are for the purpose for which they were provided, and are deleted permanently after a set period. This time period is determined by type of membership plan purchased by the user

Please note that the transfer of information by us to such third parties may involve a transfer of that information to countries outside the United Kingdom.

**Collection of Technical Information**

This website does use cookies - a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer to identify your browser - including temporary "session" cookies which enable a visitor's web browser to remember which pages on this website have already been visited and to track any referrer or affiliate information. Visitors can use this website with no substantial loss of functionality if cookies are disabled from the web browser. Technical details in connection with visits to our website and our products may be logged by us or a third party for our statistical purposes and may also be used by our online billing provider to determine the purchase price during the purchase process. No information (apart from product purchase information) is collected that could be used by us to identify website visitors. The technical details logged are confined to the following types of information:

  * The Internet Protocol address or gateway of the visitor's web server

  * The previous website address from which the visitor reached us

  * Clickstream data which shows the traffic of visitors around this web site (for example pages accessed and documents downloaded)

  * The type of web browser used by the visitor

  * The operating system of the visitor's computer

  * The screen resolution of the visitor's computer monitor

  * Information on potential security risks, URLs of websites visited that we deem potentially fraudulent and executable files that are identified as potential malware

  * Metadata regarding uploaded files such as file size, file name, file format, and other relevant parameters

**Collection of Technical Information**

You have a right to be given a copy of any personal data which you may have supplied to PDF Pro in connection with any service. You also have the right to opt out of all our data collection initiatives. To exercise either of these rights, please contact us through **the methods described above**. If you are contacting us by mail, you should include any personal identifiers which you supplied earlier (e.g. name, address, phone number, e-mail address). Your request will be dealt with as soon as possible and will take not more than 40 days to process.

You also have a right to have any inaccurate information corrected. If you discover that PDF Pro does hold inaccurate information about you, you have a right to instruct us to correct that information. Such instruction must be in writing or via our ticketing system. Your request will be dealt with as soon as possible and will take not more than 40 days to process.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

In certain circumstances you may also request that data which you have supplied to us be deleted. To exercise this right you would generally be expected to identify some contravention of data protection law in the manner in which we processes the data concerned. Please note that we may from time to time delete data which it holds about you or other persons where we consider it appropriate to do so.

**Information Sharing**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

**Changes to this policy**

Please note that we may change this policy from time to time. Any amended or material changes to this privacy policy will be posted to this website. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

_This policy was last updated on April 1, 2015_
